cemper.com 2017-12-28

# LinkResearchTools Privacy Statement - LinkResearchTools

## 1\. Data protection and legal notice

**LinkResearchTools** is committed to protecting your privacy. The provisions of this Privacy Statement apply to all of our websites and tools. They shall settle details regarding data collection and processing, and the usage of your data. By using our websites or tools, you accept these data protection provisions with all the comprised regulations and terms. If you do not agree with any of the terms and conditions stipulated in this Privacy Statement, do not use our websites and/or our tools.

## 2\. Provider and media owner

Owner, publisher, and editor:

**LinkResearchTools** GmbH  
Am Langen Felde 12 / Top 2  
1220 Vienna, Austria, Europe

**LRT Germany:**  +49 894 120 7070  
**LRT Canada:**  (204) 808-0736  
**LRT Austria:**  +43 720 883 736  
**LRT US:**  (619) 832-0736  
**LRT UK:**  +44 144 360 6363

E-mail: [feedback@LinkResearchTools.com](mailto:feedback@linkresearchtools.com)

**Link Detox** **  
** Recover – Protect – Build  

**Further information**

<http://help.linkdetox.com/>

## 3\. Legal basis

The Austrian Data Protection Act 2000 (Datenschutzgesetz 2000, DSG 2000) forms the legal basis for this Privacy Statement. Further information about the Austrian Data Protection Act [can be found here](http://www.ris.bka.gv.at/GeltendeFassung.wxe?Abfrage=Bundesnormen&Gesetzesnummer=10001597).

## 4\. Contact us

Please contact us if you have questions concerning this Privacy Statement or concerning the handling personal data. Please send an e-mail to [feedback@LinkResearchTools.com](mailto:feedback@linkresearchtools.com) or a letter to **LinkResearchTools** GmbH, Leonard-Bernstein-Strasse 10/ Floor 7, Saturn Tower, 1220 Vienna, Austria, Europe.

## 5\. Usage of our websites and tools

Or websites and tools allow users to learn more about our company, download content and provide us with contact details and other demographic information.

This information is saved on the servers of our software partner ActiveCampaign. We shall be entitled to use this information to establish contact with the visitors of our website(s), and to determine which of our company products and services are relevant to our visitors. Any and all information collected shall be subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement. We undertake to use the information collected exclusively for marketing purposes and/or lead generation.

ActiveCampaign, Inc. is a software company based in the U.S. Contact details: ActiveCampaign, Inc., 222 South Riverside Plaza, Suite 810, Chicago, IL 60606.

## 6\. Information we collect

### 6.1. Visits to our websites

You can visit our website(s) without providing any personal data. Proving personal data is only required in case you wish to use our tools. Other than that, we collect navigation information.

### 6.2. Personal data

Personal data is data which you choose to give us voluntarily that identifies you as a person. Such data may, in particular, include contact details such as e.g. name, e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, etc. Personal data may also include information about you that is available to the public on the Internet, comprising in particular information on Facebook, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, and Google.Only for the normal operation of LinkResearchTools, we may require sending some data to third parties. Such information may also be included to our work.

### 6.3. Navigation information

Navigation information includes data about your device and your visit to our website(s) and/or the usage of our tools, including in particular information about your IP-address, location, the browser type you use, referral source, duration of your visit and the pages you opened.

### 6.4. Privacy of children

Our website(s) have not been designed for children. We do not knowingly collect any personal data from children under 18. Please contact us if you suspect data has been collected from minors. We will remove such data immediately.

## 7\. Usage of collected information

### 7.1. Compliance with data protection provisions

We undertake to use any and all data collected only in strict compliance with the provisions stipulated in this Privacy Statement.

### 7.2. Refrain from selling data

We undertake to refrain from selling personal data to third parties.

### 7.3. Usage of personal data

In addition to further types of usage stipulated in this Privacy Statement, we use personal data to:

a.) improve your browser usage by personalizing the websites.

b.) send you marketing material regarding our company.

c.) to improve our free and payable offers (information and articles that cannot be accessed openly such as e.g. white papers, training courses or special seminars).

### 7.4. Usage of navigation information

We use navigation information to improve the websites and our tools. We use navigation information alone or in combination with personal data to offer and to send you personalized information regarding our company.

### 7.5. Usage of information on the usage of our tools

We use statistics showing how the different features of our tools are used. This helps us develop our tools with a greater focus on user needs.

### 7.6. Service provider

We reserve the right to hire third parties (e.g. web agencies) to provide us with services for the visitors of our website(s) and/or users of our tools. We undertake to ensure that such service providers comply with our Privacy Statement.

### 7.7. Security of personal data

We use secure technologies and procedures to protect personal data from unauthorized access. Personal data is stored on secure servers situated in safe and surveilled environments.

### 7.8. Social Media features

Our websites use Social Media features like “Facebook Share Buttons” and/or widgets like “Share this”-Buttons or other widgets. Such features can register your IP-address and record the page(s) you visited. They can also use cookies. Social Media features and widgets are provided to our websites by third parties. This Privacy Statement does not apply to such services. The terms of usage of the providers of such features are governed by their own privacy policies.

### 7.9. External websites

Our websites contain links to other websites. We shall not be obliged to verify foreign websites, nor shall be held liable for any of the content or actions on foreign websites. Our links to foreign websites do not allow any conclusions about whether or not we agree with their content or whether or not we support their website owners. This Privacy Statement does not apply to websites we link to.

### 7.10. Public forums

We offer publicly accessible forums and blogs that allow you to publish messages. Please keep in mind that any and all information you publish on publicly accessible forums and blogs on our websites may be registered and used by third parties. If you wish, we will edit or delete any information you published on our websites. We reserve the right to delete posts that contain offensive content or that are otherwise deemed inappropriate by us. Please find details under Section _9\. Unsubscribe_.

### 7.11. Storage of personal data

We keep personal data for as long as we see a reasonable possibility that such data be used for the purpose of establishing contact with regard to our subscription service. We delete such information when no longer required, although we will delete such data sooner upon request. Please find details under Section _9\. Unsubscribe_.

## 8\. Navigation information

### 8.1. Cookies

We use cookies to support you when browsing our website(s). A cookie is a small text file stored on your device via a web server. Cookies cannot import viruses or run programs on your device. One of the main reasons for using cookies is to improve your website usage by helping you save time. Cookies will tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. This will retrieve the information previously provided, allowing you to use any customized features again. You can choose to reject cookies. Most browsers accept cookies by default, but you may change your browser settings to refuse cookies. If you do so, you may not be able to use the full functionality of our website(s).

### 8.2. Log Files

We may occasionally collect and combine demographic data such as your postal code, your age, your gender and/or certain preferences via Log Files with your name or other personally identifiable information. We may also register your hardware and/or software data, including the following information: your IP-address, your browser type, the domain name, access times and referring website addresses. We use this data to enhance the quality of our offers and to create statistics about the usage of our website(s) and/or tools.

### 8.3. Clear Gifs

We use a so-called Clear Gifs software that helps us improve our subscription service by informing us which content is effective. Clear Gifs are small graphics with a unique identifier (similar to cookies) that help analyze the user behavior of website visitors. In contrast to cookies that are stored on a user’s device, Clear Gifs are invisibly embedded on websites and in e-mails and are usually about the size of a pixel. We use Clear Gifs in our HTML-based e-mails to see which e-mails were opened. We can thereby evaluate the effectiveness of communication actions and marketing activities. We combine this information with personal data. You can unsubscribe from such e-mails. Please find details under Section _9\. Unsubscribe_.

## 9\. Unsubscribe

### 9.1. Check, correct and remove personal data

If you provide us with your personal data, you will have the following rights:

a.) You may check the user data you provided.

b.) You may correct mistakes, add missing data and/or correct data that has become incorrect.

c.) You may request that your user data be not used for the purpose of establishing contact with you.

d.) You may request to have your user data removed from each and every list.

e.) You may request to have your user data deleted.

If you wish to exercise your rights, please contact us under [feedback@LinkResearchTools.com](mailto:feedback@linkresearchtools.com) or send a letter to **LinkResearchTools** GmbH, Leonard-Bernstein-Strasse 10/ Floor 7, Saturn Tower, 1220 Vienna, Austria, Europe.

Please include “Unsubscribe” in the subject. We will comply with your request as swiftly as possible, and we will notify you as soon as it has been completed.

### 9.2. Unsubscribe from our e-mail communications

You may unsubscribe from our e-mail communications at any time by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the end of the e-mail.

## 10\. Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies, text files that are stored on your device and that allow for analyzing your website usage and behavior. The information about your website usage generated via the cookie is usually transmitted to and stored by Google’s servers located in the United States. On behalf of the website owner, Google will evaluate the information in order to analyze your website behavior, to compile reports about the website activities and to render further services to the website owner related to the website and Internet usage. The IP-address transmitted from your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may reject the storage of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings of your browser; please not, however, that in this case you may not be able to use the full functionality of our websites. Furthermore, you can prevent the data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (including your IP-address) from being transferred to and/or processed by Google, by downloading and installing the following browser plugin:

https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en

## 11\. Disclaimer

We constantly review and update the content published on our websites. However, we do not assume any liability or guarantee for the current relevance, correctness and/or completeness of the information provided.
